So let's go back to our two examples,
看看我们的两个示例
医疗模型和垃圾邮件模型
the Medical Model and Spam E-mail Model.
对于医疗模型 有四种可能性
Recalled for the medical model we have four possibilities.
A true positive, which is when
真阳性 即患者生病了
我们正确地诊断出他生病了
the patient is sick and we correctly diagnosed him as sick.
A true negative, which is when the patient is
真阴性 患者没生病
我们正确地诊断为他没生病
not sick and we correctly diagnosed him as not sick.
A false positive, which is when a patient is
假阳性 患者很健康
我们错误地诊断为生病了
healthy and we incorrectly diagnosed him as sick.
最后是假阴性
And finally, a false negative,
患者生病了 我们错误地诊断为很健康
which is when the patient is sick and we incorrectly diagnosed him as healthy.
我们忽略两个正确的情形 只关注错误的情形
Now let's forget about the two correct ones and focus only on the mistakes.
下面是个小测验
Below we'll have a quiz.
Which one do you think is worse,
哪个情况更糟糕
假阳性或假阴性？
a false positive or a false negative?
换句话说 将健康人士误诊为生病了
In other words, what is a worse mistake to misdiagnose
或者将生病的患者诊断为健康人士 哪种情况更糟糕？
a healthy patient as sick or a sick patient as healthy?
回到另一个模型
Now let's go back to our other model,
即垃圾邮件模型
the Spam E-mail Model.
我们有两封邮件
So we have two emails,
一个是祖母发来的非垃圾邮件 告诉我们她烘焙了一些曲奇
one non-spam from a grandmother telling us she baked
cookies and one spam from a questionable source.
另一封是可疑人员发来的垃圾邮件
对于这个模型
Recall that for this model,
we again have four possibilities.
也有四种情况
A true positive, which is when the spam e-mail gets correctly sent into the spam folder.
真阳性即垃圾邮件正确地发送到垃圾文件夹
真阴性 即祖母的邮件
A true negative, which is when
our grandmother's e-mail gets correctly send to the Inbox folder.
正确地发送到了收件箱文件夹里
A false positive, which is when the grandmother's e-mail
假阴性 即祖母的邮件
accidentally gets sent to the spam folder.
不小心发送到了垃圾文件夹里
And finally, a false negative,
最后是假阴性
即垃圾邮件不小心发送到了收件箱里
which is when a spam e-mail accidentally gets sent to our inbox.
我们再次忽略正确的情形并仅侧重于错误的情形
Now again, let's forget about the two correct ones and focus only on the mistakes.
So below there will be another quiz.
下面是另一道测验
Which one do you think is worse,
你觉得哪种情况更糟糕
a false positive or a false negative?
假阳性或假阴性？
In other words, what is a worst mistake?
换句话说 哪个错误最糟糕？
To accidentally send your grandmother's e-mail to
不小心将祖母的电子邮件发送到垃圾文件夹
the spam folder or to accidentally send the spam e-mail into your inbox?
或不小心将垃圾邮件发到收件箱里？
Enter your answers below.
请将答案填在下方